Today's big up goes to the black people that did not show up to Trump's round table.
So this man went to a black church in Detroit, Michigan to hold a Blacks for Trump round table.
But here's where it gets interesting.
The church located in a predominantly black city, it was packed with white people.
Oh, really?
You know, here's some advice.
The next time you decide to have a Blacks for Trump round table in a black church,
you might want to have some neat rosy.
I don't know. I just, you know, I don't know.
That's just my thought.
Today's lockdown goes to kids doing the most with these internet pranks.
An internet streamer thought it would be hilarious to prank a bodybuilder at the gym.
Spoiler alert, it was not.
This prankster spotted Bradley Martin, a YouTube bodybuilder who's known for his strength and fitness videos.
Instead of just going over there and saying, like your videos, bro, this prankster thought, I know what I'm going to do.
So he went and snatched Bradley's hat off his head.
After calmly asking for it back, Bradley decided enough was enough, reached out, grabbed his cap, and smacked the sonic rings.
Yes. I like that.
I like that.
Out this boy's face.
After things calmed down, Bradley let the prankster have one slap back.
I mean, there were no lawsuits.
Just a solid lesson in respecting personal space.
Also, y'all be taking these pranks way too far.